ARYN WEATHERLY

Software Developer

ABOUT ME

Energetic, hard-working and resilient. Lover of books, science, puzzles, art and video games. I attended school for massage therapy, radiology technology and physical therapy. I spent many years working in the health field only to realize I wanted to do something else with my life. It wasn't until a friend suggested I look into programming that I really felt I found what I was meant to do for the rest of my life.

EDUCATION

2012 - 2016 • University of Tennessee at Chattanooga BS in Exercise Science

August 2019 - present • Nashville Software School Full stack web-developer

EXPERIENCE

2011-2015 Salon Capelli Day Spa and Boutique

Receptionist

- Tasked to price products, schedule appointments, handle the register and do chores around the store.
- Opened and closed the store each day.

2011-2013 X-clusive Boutique

Sales Associate and Model

• Tasked with organizing the store, working the register, and modeling clothing for the store website.

2016-2017 Personal Trainer

- Tasked with helping clients change their lives for the better through exercise programs and diet plans.
- Created individualized workout schedules, assisted and instructed clients on how to properly use workout equipment. Motivated and encouraged clients.

May 2019- Beaded Bungalow

present Designer and Sales associate

• Worked closely with clients to create one of a kind pieces of jewelry and repair broken pieces.

2018- Jewelry By Arynpresent Jewelry Deisgner

• Designed, created and sold one of a kind pieces of jewelry to clients.

SKILLS

TECH

- CSS, Bootstrap,
- Reactstrap, Bulma
- HTML, Javascript, React.js, C#,

PERSONAL

- Hardworking, resilient, motivated and eager to learn.
- Spanish translator

CONTACT INFORMATION

PHONE

(615) 428-4487

EMAIL

Arynweatherly93@gmail.com

LINKEDIN

https://www.linkedin.com/in/aryn-weatherly

GITHUB

https://github.com/Arynweatherly